Разноцветные глаза
Different-colored eyes
Волосы цвета огня
Hair the color of fire
Пару личностей во мне
A couple of personalities within me
Будь поосторожней
Be more careful
Искупи свои грехи
Atone for your sins
Мы священные огни
We are sacred flames
Мы не так плохи
We're not as bad
Как ты думаешь
As you think
Подойди ко мне на шаг
Come a step toward me
Подними свой белый флаг
Raise your white flag
Искусаю до крови
I'll bite until there's blood
Пощады не проси
Don't ask for mercy
Растворившись в тишине
Dissolving into silence
Голос твой на глубине
Your voice in the depths
Тайну расскажет реке
Will tell a secret to the river
Я кажусь тебе другой
I seem different to you
Хочешь, получи любовь
If you want, receive love
Но не забывай, что это дар не мой
But don't forget that this gift isn't mine
Не стоило смотреть в мои глаза
You should not have looked into my eyes
И не утони потом в своих слезах
And don't drown afterward in your tears
На ветру белое платье
A white dress in the wind
На тебе проклятье
A curse upon you
Мне нужны объятия, поцелуи, счастье
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
Разлетелся пепел боли
The ashes of pain scattered
Я бегу по полю
I run through the field
С тобою в небеса
With you into the heavens
Мы с тобой как волшебство
You and I are like magic
Жаль, в конце ждёт ничего
Too bad, nothing awaits at the end
Я не знаю как нам быть
I don't know what we should do
Будет проще отпустить
It will be easier to let go
Мне казалось ты любил
It seemed to me you loved
Но в глаза кидал мне пыль
But you were deceiving me
Книга жизни возгорит
The book of life will burn
Больше не найдёшь страниц
You'll find no more pages
Не стоило смотреть в мои глаза
You should not have looked into my eyes
И не утони потом в своих слезах
And don't drown afterward in your tears
На ветру белое платье
A white dress in the wind
На тебе проклятье
A curse upon you
Мне нужны объятия, поцелуи, счастье
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
Разлетелся пепел боли
The ashes of pain scattered
Я бегу по полю
I run through the field
С тобою в небеса
With you into the heavens
На ветру белое платье
A white dress in the wind
На тебе проклятье
A curse upon you
Мне нужны объятия, поцелуи, счастье
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
Разлетелся пепел боли
The ashes of pain scattered
Я бегу по полю
I run through the field
С тобою в небеса
With you into the heavens
На ветру белое платье
A white dress in the wind
На тебе проклятье
A curse upon you
Мне нужны объятия, поцелуи, счастье
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
Разлетелся пепел боли
The ashes of pain scattered
Я бегу по полю
I run through the field
С тобою в небеса
With you into the heavens